[
{
    "Question": "Which author wrote 'The War of the Jewels'?",
    "correctAnswer": "J. R. R. Tolkien",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "G. K. Chesterton",
            "Philip Pullman",
            "C. S. Lewis"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f38"
},
{
    "Question": "What Would You Traditionally 'Bob' For At Halloween?",
    "correctAnswer": "Apples",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Bananas",
            "Cherries",
            "Carrots"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951889"
},
{
    "Question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Some Like It Hot'?",
    "correctAnswer": "\"Well, nobody's perfect.\"",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "\"Nobody puts Baby in a corner.\"",
            "\"My mother thanks you. My father thanks you. My sister thanks you. And I thank you.\"",
            "\"I'll have what she's having.\""
    ],
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fc22"
},
{
    "Question": "Which author wrote 'Madame Bovary'?",
    "correctAnswer": "Gustave Flaubert",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Anatole France",
            "Guy de Maupassant",
            "Charles Perrault"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950e2c"
},
{
    "Question": "Which company, with a name formed by contracting the Danish words for 'play well', was founded by carpenter Ole Kristiansen in 1932?",
    "correctAnswer": "Lego",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Playmobil",
            "Nintendo",
            "Mattel"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951732"
},
{
    "Question": "Which actor played the role of Jeff Spicoli in Fast Times at Ridgemont High?",
    "correctAnswer": "Sean Penn",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "James Stewart",
            "Johnny Depp",
            "Arnold Schwarzenegger"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8c1"
},
{
    "Question": "When was the first SMS message sent?",
    "correctAnswer": "1992",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "1987",
            "1997",
            "2002"
    ],
    "id": "62611fdb4b176d54800e3d75"
},
{
    "Question": "In the world of sport what has the maximum dimensions of 60 metres by 30 metres?",
    "correctAnswer": "An Ice Skating Rink",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "A Football Pitch",
            "A Tennis Court",
            "A Rugby Pitch"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9500a8"
},
{
    "Question": "Which author wrote 'Dubliners'?",
    "correctAnswer": "James Joyce",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Samuel Beckett",
            "Oscar Wilde",
            "Jonathan Swift"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950ec5"
},
{
    "Question": "Which German rock band released the song 'Still Loving You'?",
    "correctAnswer": "Scorpions",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Rammstein",
            "Sodom",
            "U.D.O."
    ],
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950bde"
},
{
    "Question": "Chicory root is used in a substitute for which drink?",
    "correctAnswer": "Coffee\u00a0",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Wine",
            "Beer",
            "Cola"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f9515e5"
},
{
    "Question": "What is the word for a male llama?",
    "correctAnswer": "A Macho",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "A Buck",
            "A Boar",
            "A Hob"
    ],
    "id": "62433498cfaae40c12961453"
},
{
    "Question": "Which of these is a basketball team based in Sacramento?",
    "correctAnswer": "Sacramento Kings",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Sacramento Flames",
            "Sacramento Blackhawks",
            "Sacramento Trailblazers"
    ],
    "id": "62417d980f96c4efe8d773d7"
},
{
    "Question": "Which of these countries borders Pakistan?",
    "correctAnswer": "People's Republic of China",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Tajikistan",
            "Kyrgyzstan",
            "Uzbekistan"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950a3d"
},
{
    "Question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Old School'?",
    "correctAnswer": "\"We\u2019re goin\u2019 streaking!\"",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "\"No wire hangers, ever!\"",
            "\"Listen to them. Children of the night. What music they make.\"",
            "\"You've got to ask yourself one question: 'Do I feel lucky?' Well, do ya, punk?\""
    ],
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbea"
},
{
    "Question": "Which of the following describes Antoine Laurent Lavoisier?",
    "correctAnswer": "Chemist who had a leading impact on the chemical revolution.",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Improved the Newcomen steam engine creating an efficient steam engine.",
            "King of Macedonia and military leader.",
            "Liberator of Latin American countries."
    ],
    "id": "6293ebed7f41d6338b96eeca"
},
{
    "Question": "What type of instrument is a oboe?",
    "correctAnswer": "Woodwind",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Brass",
            "Stringed",
            "Percussion"
    ],
    "id": "6266bc10b0e62e469cf43e8b"
},
{
    "Question": "What are male cows called?",
    "correctAnswer": "Bulls",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Fellas",
            "Dogs",
            "Blokes"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c3f7cc59eab6f95237c"
},
{
    "Question": "Which of these countries borders South Africa?",
    "correctAnswer": "Zimbabwe",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Zambia",
            "Angola",
            "Malawi"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950a38"
},
{
    "Question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Not for the first time, an argument had broken out over breakfast at number four, Privet drive'?",
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "The Sea of Monsters",
            "The Battle of the Labyrinth",
            "The Lightning Thief"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501c0"
},
{
    "Question": "Which English rock band released the song 'Here Comes the Sun'?",
    "correctAnswer": "The Beatles",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "The Who",
            "The Clash",
            "Pink Floyd"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950d11"
},
{
    "Question": "Where would you find the city of Nur Sultan?",
    "correctAnswer": "Kazakhstan",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Kyrgyzstan",
            "Tajikistan",
            "Azerbaijan"
    ],
    "id": "6260308b4b176d54800e3d2c"
},
{
    "Question": "Which singer released the song 'If It's Lovin' that You Want'?",
    "correctAnswer": "Rihanna",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Drake",
            "Nicki Minaj",
            "Ricky Martin"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fe8d"
},
{
    "Question": "The \"canebrake\", \"timber\" and \"pygmy\" are types of what\"",
    "correctAnswer": "Rattlesnake",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Coyote",
            "Goose",
            "Pig"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f9510a8"
},
{
    "Question": "Which English rock band released the song 'See Emily Play'?",
    "correctAnswer": "Pink Floyd",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Wings",
            "Rudimental",
            "The Alan Parsons Project"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950ca1"
},
{
    "Question": "What is the word for a young moose?",
    "correctAnswer": "A Calf",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "A Caterpillar",
            "A Kit",
            "A Lamb"
    ],
    "id": "624334c1cfaae40c12961463"
},
{
    "Question": "What is the capital city of Bangladesh?",
    "correctAnswer": "Dhaka",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Vilnius",
            "Rabat",
            "Lusaka"
    ],
    "id": "62373f93cb85f7ce9e949ca6"
},
{
    "Question": "Which film won the Academy Award for Best Picture in 1952?",
    "correctAnswer": "The Greatest Show on Earth",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "High Noon",
            "Ivanhoe",
            "Moulin Rouge"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb7f"
},
{
    "Question": "What is Taxology the study of?",
    "correctAnswer": "a synonym for taxonomy",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "the phylum Bryozoa",
            "interactions among organisms and the water cycle",
            "a branch of theology concerned with the final events in the history of the world or of mankind"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95047f"
},
{
    "Question": "Niamey is the capital city of which country?",
    "correctAnswer": "Niger",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Kyrgyzstan",
            "Belize",
            "Israel"
    ],
    "id": "623741afcb85f7ce9e949d7f"
},
{
    "Question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A working-class bouncer becomes the driver of an African-American classical pianist.'",
    "correctAnswer": "Green Book",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Platoon",
            "V for Vendetta",
            "The Dark Knight"
    ],
    "id": "625740759da29df7b05f73df"
},
{
    "Question": "A heavenly body moving under the attraction of the Sun and consisting of a nucleus and a tail is a(n) _______.",
    "correctAnswer": "Comet",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Meteor",
            "Moon",
            "Satellite"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f9510da"
},
{
    "Question": "Which of these is a baseball team based in Washington?",
    "correctAnswer": "Washington Nationals",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Washington Saints",
            "Washington Dolphins",
            "Washington Bucks"
    ],
    "id": "62417dd20f96c4efe8d773ed"
},
{
    "Question": "Which artist painted \"The Sleepers\"",
    "correctAnswer": "Gustave Courbet",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Caravaggio",
            "Ren\u00e9 Magritte",
            "\u200ePablo Picasso"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f9f1"
},
{
    "Question": "Which song begins with the lyrics: \"Old man, look at my life / I'm a lot like you were...\"?",
    "correctAnswer": "\"Old Man\" by Neil Young",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "\"Jumpin', Jumpin'\" by Destiny's Child",
            "\"What I Got\" by Sublime",
            "\"Let's Go Crazy\" by Prince and The Revolution"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbbb"
},
{
    "Question": "Which English-Australian pop group released the album 'Horizontal'?",
    "correctAnswer": "Bee Gees",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Level 42",
            "Culture Club",
            "Dire Straits"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950c4f"
},
{
    "Question": "In which country would you find the City of Dubrovnik?",
    "correctAnswer": "Croatia",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Libya",
            "Italy",
            "Ecuador"
    ],
    "id": "623b5804fd6c701a92118391"
},
{
    "Question": "Which American singer, songwriter, and actress released the studio album 'The Fame'?",
    "correctAnswer": "Lady Gaga",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Hikaru Utada",
            "Drake",
            "Madonna"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fe9a"
},
{
    "Question": "Which of these cities is in United Kingdom?",
    "correctAnswer": "Glasgow",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Baltimore",
            "Houston",
            "Minneapolis-St Paul"
    ],
    "id": "62602dc44b176d54800e3cac"
},
{
    "Question": "In which year was Fargo first released in the cinema?",
    "correctAnswer": "1996",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "1992",
            "2000",
            "2004"
    ],
    "id": "625fd725dc0dd3b72da64d26"
},
{
    "Question": "Which wizard was portrayed by Christopher Lee in The Lord Of The Rings?",
    "correctAnswer": "Saruman",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Gandalf",
            "Radagast",
            "Merlin"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9517df"
},
{
    "Question": "Which director directed Inception?",
    "correctAnswer": "Christopher Nolan",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Steven Spielberg",
            "Woody Allen",
            "Martin Scorsese"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501f3"
},
{
    "Question": "Which country's flag can be described as 'Green with a yellow diamond in the center with a blue celestial globe.'?",     
    "correctAnswer": "Brazil",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Jamaica",
            "Faroe Islands",
            "Iran"
    ],
    "id": "625e9dff796f721e95543f38"
},
{
    "Question": "What is Tribology the study of?",
    "correctAnswer": "friction and lubrication",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "cetaceans - whales, dolphins, and porpoise",
            "the ecological interrelationships among communities of organisms",
            "the process of human psychological evolution"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950472"
},
{
    "Question": "In which country would you find the UNESCO World Heritage site of Al-Hijr Archaeological Site?",
    "correctAnswer": "Saudi Arabia",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Thailand",
            "Mexico",
            "Israel"
    ],
    "id": "623b57cafd6c701a9211837d"
},
{
    "Question": "Which film won the Academy Award for Best Picture in 1983?",
    "correctAnswer": "Terms of Endearment",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "The Big Chill",
            "The Dresser",
            "The Right Stuff"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb48"
},
{
    "Question": "Which actor has featured in films including Thor and The Silence of the Lambs?",
    "correctAnswer": "Anthony Hopkins",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Tom Hanks",
            "Ewan McGregor",
            "Arnold Schwarzenegger"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9507ac"
},
{
    "Question": "Who won the 2002 Academy Award for Best Leading Actress for playing the role of Virginia Woolf in The Hours?",
    "correctAnswer": "Nicole Kidman",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Salma Hayek",
            "Diane Lane",
            "Julianne Moore"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb08"
},
{
    "Question": "What is the name given to the art of miniaturising trees and maintaining their small size?",
    "correctAnswer": "Bonsai",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Ornamental Shrubbery",
            "Decorage",
            "Topiary"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951067"
},
{
    "Question": "What is the capital of Equatorial Guinea?",
    "correctAnswer": "Malabo",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Yaonde",
            "Luanda",
            "Bissau"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ffbd"
},
{
    "Question": "Which animal appears on the Bacardi Logo?",
    "correctAnswer": "Bat\u00a0",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Dog",
            "Cat",
            "Horse"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950240"
},
{
    "Question": "Taco had a one hit wonder in 1983 with which song?",
    "correctAnswer": "Puttin' on the Ritz",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Barbie Girl",
            "Turn the Beat Around",
            "What I Am"
    ],
    "id": "625064a7e12f6dec240bdfc3"
},
{
    "Question": "The pasta gemelli has what meaning in Italian?",
    "correctAnswer": "Twins",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Squid-like",
            "Pens",
            "Bibs"
    ],
    "id": "625006b30d86c8f685d80ef6"
},
{
    "Question": "Which band includes 'Jared Leto'?",
    "correctAnswer": "Thirty Seconds to Mars",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Counting Crows",
            "Three 6 Mafia",
            "The Velvet Underground"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b4a"
},
{
    "Question": "What city was destroyed by a 'little boy'?",
    "correctAnswer": "Hiroshima",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Jericho",
            "Babel",
            "Dresden"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9519d2"
},
{
    "Question": "Where in the world are bell peppers originally from?",
    "correctAnswer": "Central America",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "China",
            "Central Asia",
            "Europe"
    ],
    "id": "624ab07ac64ce21c11f06e9f"
},
{
    "Question": "Where would you find the city of Petaling Jaya?",
    "correctAnswer": "Malaysia",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Philippines",
            "Vietnam",
            "Singapore"
    ],
    "id": "62602ff84b176d54800e3d07"
},
{
    "Question": "What type of instrument is a double bass?",
    "correctAnswer": "Stringed",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Percussion",
            "Woodwind",
            "Brass"
    ],
    "id": "6266bc3bff2394bd44dee000"
},
{
    "Question": "Which actor played the role of The Dude in The Big Lebowski?",
    "correctAnswer": "Jeff Bridges",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Michael Douglas",
            "Errol Flynn",
            "John Wayne"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8ec"
},
{
    "Question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Harry Potter was a highly unusual boy in many ways.'?",
    "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince",
            "New Moon",
            "The Alchemist"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501bd"
},
{
    "Question": "Which director directed Solo: A Star Wars Story?",
    "correctAnswer": "Ron Howard",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Steven Spielberg",
            "Woody Allen",
            "Martin Scorsese"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95020c"
},
{
    "Question": "Which of these countries borders Sweden?",
    "correctAnswer": "Finland",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Poland",
            "Lithuania",
            "Latvia"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950ad8"
},
{
    "Question": "From which part of the world do blueberries originate?",
    "correctAnswer": "North America",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Southeast Asia",
            "Central Asia",
            "Europe"
    ],
    "id": "624ab05fc64ce21c11f06e95"
},
{
    "Question": "What is the capital city of Egypt?",
    "correctAnswer": "Cairo",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Conakry",
            "Nairobi",
            "Alexandria"
    ],
    "id": "6237404ccb85f7ce9e949cf0"
},
{
    "Question": " What was Sir Henry Morgan famous for in the 17th century?",
    "correctAnswer": "Pirate",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Judge",
            "Prime Minister",
            "General"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951a6c"
},
{
    "Question": "Where would you find the city of Asuncion?",
    "correctAnswer": "Paraguay",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Brazil",
            "Jamaica",
            "Mexico"
    ],
    "id": "626030aa4b176d54800e3d35"
},
{
    "Question": "What is the marketing slogan of Kelloggs Frosties?",
    "correctAnswer": "They're GR-R-R-reat!",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "A glass and a half in every half pound",
            "Finger lickin' good",
            "Breakfast of Champions"
    ],
    "id": "626288a14b176d54800e3daa"
},
{
    "Question": "Which band includes 'Bj\u00f6rn Ulvaeus'?",
    "correctAnswer": "ABBA",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "In Flames",
            "HammerFall",
            "Katatonia"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950d97"
},
{
    "Question": "Which band includes 'Angus Young'?",
    "correctAnswer": "AC/DC",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Pendulum",
            "INXS",
            "Savage Garden"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950d7f"
},
{
    "Question": "Which region of the world uses '.ru' at the end of its web addresses?",
    "correctAnswer": "Russia",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Peru",
            "Uruguay",
            "Romania"
    ],
    "id": "623735bccfe13103f55eb562"
},
{
    "Question": "Which band includes 'Joseph Hahn'?",
    "correctAnswer": "Linkin Park",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Alice in Chains",
            "Hollywood Undead",
            "System of a Down"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950daa"
},
{
    "Question": "Which British rock band released the studio album 'Jazz'?",
    "correctAnswer": "Queen",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Level 42",
            "Deep Purple",
            "Feeder"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950cd3"
},
{
    "Question": "Which book contains the character 'Meursault'?",
    "correctAnswer": "The Stranger",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "One Hundred Years of Solitude",
            "The Trial",
            "The Quiet American"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f975"
},
{
    "Question": "Which artist painted \"The Great Wave off Kanagawa\"",
    "correctAnswer": "Hokusai",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "\u200ePablo Picasso",
            "Vasily Kandinsky",
            "Gustave Courbet"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f9f2"
},
{
    "Question": "Which actor has featued in films including The Big Lebowski and Transformers?",
    "correctAnswer": "John Turturro",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Jean-Claude Van Damme",
            "Pierce Brosnan",
            "Russell Crowe"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9506c2"
},
{
    "Question": "Who was defeated at the Battle of Little Bighorn?",
    "correctAnswer": "General Custer",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "General Lee",
            "General Grant",
            "General Nelson"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951bef"
},
{
    "Question": "Frankfort is the capital of which US state?",
    "correctAnswer": "Kentucky",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Arizona",
            "Montana",
            "Idaho"
    ],
    "id": "623375a062eaad73716a86be"
},
{
    "Question": "What is the word for a male pig?",
    "correctAnswer": "A Boar",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "A Macho",
            "A Bull",
            "A Hob"
    ],
    "id": "624334f3cfaae40c12961477"
},
{
    "Question": "Which author wrote 'Poirot Investigates'?",
    "correctAnswer": "Agatha Christie",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Robert Louis Stevenson",
            "Charles Dickens",
            "Lewis Carroll"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f8b"
},
{
    "Question": "What is Lymphology the study of?",
    "correctAnswer": "the lymph system and glands",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "measurement",
            "human beings killing other human beings",
            "grasses"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950500"
},
{
    "Question": "Which of these is a popular drink in The Dominican Republic?",
    "correctAnswer": "Mama Juana",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Gin",
            "Maotai",
            "Chibuku"
    ],
    "id": "6271644a1ba117625baac955"
},
{
    "Question": "With which sport is Jackie Joyner-Kersee associated?",
    "correctAnswer": "Athletics",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Tennis",
            "Rugby Union",
            "Table tennis"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8af"
},
{
    "Question": "Who played the role of James Bond in Moonraker?",
    "correctAnswer": "Roger Moore",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Timothy Dalton",
            "Daniel Craig",
            "George Lazenby"
    ],
    "id": "624db9d3de6018633d31f6a4"
},
{
    "Question": "Which word is defined as 'to disconcert of confuse'?",
    "correctAnswer": "Discombobulate",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Cacophony",
            "Dragoman",
            "Dragoman"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc8a"
},
{
    "Question": "In which year was A Beautiful Mind released?",
    "correctAnswer": "2001",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "1998",
            "2004",
            "2007"
    ],
    "id": "625fd700dc0dd3b72da64d1b"
},
{
    "Question": "Which film contains the character 'Frank Booth'?",
    "correctAnswer": "Blue Velvet",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Network",
            "Alien",
            "Apocalypse Now"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f92f"
},
{
    "Question": "Which American singer released the song 'I'm Not a Girl, Not Yet a Woman'?",
    "correctAnswer": "Britney Spears",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Madonna",
            "Nicki Minaj",
            "Aretha Franklin"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fde5"
},
{
    "Question": "Dal Bhaath is a dish that is most associated with which part of the world?",
    "correctAnswer": "India",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Barbados",
            "Georgia",
            "Peru"
    ],
    "id": "624c60d850d1a5e051325a77"
},
{
    "Question": "What song did Devo have a hit with in 1980?",
    "correctAnswer": "Whip It",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Epic",
            "I Touch Myself",
            "Mambo No. 5 (A Little Bit Of...)"
    ],
    "id": "625063ebe12f6dec240bdf8c"
},
{
    "Question": "Dia de los Muertos (The Day of the Dead) is celebrated in which Latin American country?",
    "correctAnswer": "Mexico",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Ecuador",
            "Guatemala",
            "Bolivia"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950452"
},
{
    "Question": "What type of fish is in an omelette Arnold Bennett?",
    "correctAnswer": "Smoked Haddock",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Pickled Herring",
            "Spiced Basa",
            "Battered Cod"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95029a"
},
{
    "Question": "Halifax is the capital of which Canadian province?",
    "correctAnswer": "Nova Scotia",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Quebec",
            "Labrador",
            "Alberta"
    ],
    "id": "623375c162eaad73716a86c5"
},
{
    "Question": "Where would you find the city of Tegucigalpa?",
    "correctAnswer": "Honduras",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Dominican Republic",
            "Mexico",
            "Cuba"
    ],
    "id": "626030bb4b176d54800e3d3a"
},
{
    "Question": "The country of Belize is on which continent?",
    "correctAnswer": "North America",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "South America",
            "Oceania",
            "Europe"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950803"
},
{
    "Question": "Which dish contains offal and oatmeal, and is traditionally boiled in a bag made from the stomach of an animal?",        
    "correctAnswer": "Haggis\u00a0",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Pieds Paquets",
            "Papaitan",
            "Fois Grois"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95025c"
},
{
    "Question": "Which city lies on the east side of San Francisco Bay?",
    "correctAnswer": "Oakland",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Washington, D.C.",
            "Los Angeles",
            "Philadelphia"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff7b"
},
{
    "Question": "Which Instrument Measures Atmospheric Pressure?",
    "correctAnswer": "A Barometer\u00a0",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "A Hydrometer",
            "A Meterometer",
            "An Atmoseter"
    ],
    "id": "623388230161109f922aac6a"
},
{
    "Question": "In which year was The Wizard of Oz released?",
    "correctAnswer": "1939",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "1915",
            "1923",
            "1931"
    ],
    "id": "625fd741dc0dd3b72da64d2e"
},
{
    "Question": "What is Genecology the study of?",
    "correctAnswer": "genetic differences in relation to the environment",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "a discipline that attempts to reconstruct the transmission of a text on the basis of relations between the various surviving manuscripts",
            "study of devil worshipers",
            "human growth"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95052f"
},
{
    "Question": "What is the symbol for copper?",
    "correctAnswer": "Cu",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Cp",
            "Cm",
            "Co"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951022"
},
{
    "Question": "With which sport is Martina Navratilova associated?",
    "correctAnswer": "Tennis",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
            "Table tennis",
            "Gymnastics",
            "Motor Racing"
    ],
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8bc"
}
]